<boards version="2.0">
    <board default_location="local">
        <id>VELA_IF310_DVK</id>
        <category>AIROC&#8482; Connectivity BSPs</category>
        <board_uri>https://github.com/Ezurio/TARGET_VELA_IF310_DVK</board_uri>
        <chips>
            <mcu>CYW55310IUBGT</mcu>
            <radio>CYW55310IUBGT</radio>
        </chips>
        <name>VELA_IF310_DVK</name>
        <summary>The Infineon CYW55310 is a low-power, single-chip device that supports Bluetooth&#174;/Bluetooth&#174; Low Energy 5.3, including Basic Rate (BDR), Enhanced Data Rate (EDR), and Bluetooth&#174; Low Energy. The device supports LE audio with LC3 codec, LE long range, LE 2 Mbps, LE mesh, LE isochronous channels, and advertising extensions. It features integrated on-chip power amplifiers with 0 dBm, +13 dBm, and +19 dBm output power paths optimized for best efficiency, an integrated power management unit (PMU), 768 KB SRAM, 2048 KB ROM, and a 4-wire UART host interface. The CYW55310 is designed for IoT devices requiring minimal power consumption and compact size, targeting applications such as smart watches, smart glasses, AR/VR devices, IP cameras, door locks, and smart speakers. It operates over the -40&#176;C to +85&#176;C temperature range and is available in a 0.35 mm pitch WLBGA package.</summary>
        <prov_capabilities>arduino bsp_gen4 bt cat5 cyw55513 cyw55xxx cyw955513evk_01 flash_0k hal i2c i2s led low_power mcu_gp memory pdm qspi rtc sdio pot spi sram_768k switch tdm uart wifi</prov_capabilities>
        <description>        &lt;div class="category"&gt;Kit Features:&lt;/div&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;         &lt;li&gt;CYW55310 Bluetooth&#174;/Bluetooth&#174; Low Energy 5.3 single-chip solution&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;Supports BDR, EDR, LE audio (LC3 codec), LE long range, LE 2 Mbps, LE mesh, and advertising extensions&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;Dual TDM/I2S audio interfaces supporting HFP, A2DP, and LE audio use cases&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;PDM interface for digital microphone connectivity&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;USB Type-C connector for power, programming, and USB-UART bridge&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p/&gt;         &lt;div class="category"&gt;Kit Contents:&lt;/div&gt;         &lt;ul&gt;         &lt;li&gt;VELA IF310 DVK evaluation board&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;M.2 to FFC adapter board&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;30-pin FFC cable&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;USB Type-C to Type-C cable&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;Six jumper wires (5 inches each)&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;li&gt;Quick Start Guide&lt;/li&gt;         &lt;/ul&gt;</description>
        <documentation_url>https://www.ezurio.com/wireless-modules/bluetooth-modules/vela-if310-bluetooth-6-classic-and-le-module</documentation_url>
        <versions>
            <version tools_min_version="3.2.0" flow_version="2.0" prov_capabilities_per_version="bsp_gen4">
                <num>v0.2.99</num>
                <commit>release-v0.2.99</commit>
            </version>
        </versions>
    </board>
</boards>
